(Penny:)Okay. How do you know he said that?
You left the room.
(Leonard:)Hey, do you want me to finish
working on your man-feet or not?
(Penny:)Fine. Go ahead.
WOMAN:
Howard, are you having a playdate?!
(Past Howard:)I don't have playdates! I have colleagues!
Do their parents know they're here?!
(Past Howard:)No, but if you keep screaming,
maybe they'll hear you!
(Past Leonard:)That your dad?
(Past Howard:)She grows any more hair on her face, yes.
(Past Leonard:)Oh, man. Is that a two-stage rocket?
(Past Howard:)Three. I designed the engine myself.
(Past Raj:)Cool. Can it break Mach 1?
(Past Howard:)Oh, probably, if I could get
my hands on that new fuel...
(Past Howard:)...the government's been working on.
(Past Leonard:)Oh, this just might be your lucky day.
WOMAN: Howard, what happened to
the Oreos I left on the counter?!